{
    "subject": "Cliff_Robertson",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "J._W._Coop",
    "human_readable": "Cliff Robertson directed J.W. Coop.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9196469783782959,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Cliff Robertson."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8675824403762817,
            "question": "Is Cliff Robertson known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8275265693664551,
            "question": "Who directed the film J.W. Coop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8211413025856018,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Cliff Robertson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6868359446525574,
            "question": "What was the role of Cliff Robertson in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6309915781021118,
            "question": "Who is J.W. Coop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5701389312744141,
            "question": "What type of work did Cliff Robertson do in the film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5651719570159912,
            "question": "What other films has Cliff Robertson been involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49749574065208435,
            "question": "Was J.W. Coop a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3935234248638153,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Cliff Robertson's career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cliff Robertson directed J.W. Coop.",
            "html": "yago_22830_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was J.W. Coop a successful film?",
            "html": "yago_22830_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other films has Cliff Robertson been involved in?",
            "html": "yago_22830_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work did Cliff Robertson do in the film industry?",
            "html": "yago_22830_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22830_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22830_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22830_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22830_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22830_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22830_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22830_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22830_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22830_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22830_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Cliff Robertson directed J.W. Coop\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple documents that mention Cliff Robertson's involvement in the film J.W. Coop, including:\n\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_22830/re-ranker-msmarco/80.txt:\n  * \"Directed by CLIFF ROBERTSON\"\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_22830/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt:\n  * \"Cliff Robertson (director, screenwriter, starring)\"\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_22830/re-ranker-msmarco/93.txt:\n  * \"Cliff Robertson (director, screenwriter, starring)\"\n\nAll of these documents confirm that Cliff Robertson was the director of the film J.W. Coop."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Cliff Robertson directed the film J.W. Coop, supporting the statement that Cliff Robertson directed J.W. Coop."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}